<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
	<dictionary>
		<commentId>
			<label>commentId</label>
			<comment/>
			<maxlength>22</maxlength>
			<notProvided>The commentId field is required but was not provided.</notProvided>
			<invalidType>The commentId field does not contain valid data.  This field must be a numeric value.</invalidType>
			<invalidLength>The commentId field is too long.  This field must be no more than 22 bytes long.</invalidLength>
		</commentId>
		<comment>
			<label>comment</label>
			<comment/>
			<maxlength>4000</maxlength>
			<notProvided>The comment field is required but was not provided.</notProvided>
			<invalidType>The comment field does not contain valid data.  This field must be a string value.</invalidType>
			<invalidLength>The comment field is too long.  This field must be no more than 4000 bytes long.</invalidLength>
		</comment>
		<posted>
			<label>posted</label>
			<comment/>
			<maxlength>7</maxlength>
			<notProvided>The posted field is required but was not provided.</notProvided>
			<invalidType>The posted field does not contain valid data.  This field must be a date value.</invalidType>
			<invalidLength>The posted field is too long.  This field must be no more than 7 bytes long.</invalidLength>
		</posted>
		<subscribe>
			<label>subscribe</label>
			<comment/>
			<maxlength>1</maxlength>
			<notProvided>The subscribe field is required but was not provided.</notProvided>
			<invalidType>The subscribe field does not contain valid data.  This field must be a string value.</invalidType>
			<invalidLength>The subscribe field is too long.  This field must be no more than 1 bytes long.</invalidLength>
		</subscribe>
		<emailAddress>
			<label>emailAddress</label>
			<comment/>
			<maxlength>50</maxlength>
			<invalidType>The emailAddress field does not contain valid data.  This field must be a string value.</invalidType>
			<invalidLength>The emailAddress field is too long.  This field must be no more than 50 bytes long.</invalidLength>
		</emailAddress>
		<name>
			<label>name</label>
			<comment/>
			<maxlength>50</maxlength>
			<notProvided>The name field is required but was not provided.</notProvided>
			<invalidType>The name field does not contain valid data.  This field must be a string value.</invalidType>
			<invalidLength>The name field is too long.  This field must be no more than 50 bytes long.</invalidLength>
		</name>
		<entryId>
			<label>entryId</label>
			<comment/>
			<maxlength>22</maxlength>
			<notProvided>The entryId field is required but was not provided.</notProvided>
			<invalidType>The entryId field does not contain valid data.  This field must be a numeric value.</invalidType>
			<invalidLength>The entryId field is too long.  This field must be no more than 22 bytes long.</invalidLength>
		</entryId>
	</dictionary>
