<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
	<dictionary>
		<USERID>
			<label>USERID</label>
			<comment/>
			<maxlength>22</maxlength>
			<notProvided>The USERID field is required but was not provided.</notProvided>
			<invalidType>The USERID field does not contain valid data.  This field must be a numeric value.</invalidType>
			<invalidLength>The USERID field is too long.  This field must be no more than 22 bytes long.</invalidLength>
		</USERID>
		<PASSWORD>
			<label>PASSWORD</label>
			<comment/>
			<maxlength>20</maxlength>
			<notProvided>The PASSWORD field is required but was not provided.</notProvided>
			<invalidType>The PASSWORD field does not contain valid data.  This field must be a string value.</invalidType>
			<invalidLength>The PASSWORD field is too long.  This field must be no more than 20 bytes long.</invalidLength>
		</PASSWORD>
		<LASTNAME>
			<label>LASTNAME</label>
			<comment/>
			<maxlength>20</maxlength>
			<notProvided>The LASTNAME field is required but was not provided.</notProvided>
			<invalidType>The LASTNAME field does not contain valid data.  This field must be a string value.</invalidType>
			<invalidLength>The LASTNAME field is too long.  This field must be no more than 20 bytes long.</invalidLength>
		</LASTNAME>
		<USERNAME>
			<label>USERNAME</label>
			<comment/>
			<maxlength>20</maxlength>
			<notProvided>The USERNAME field is required but was not provided.</notProvided>
			<invalidType>The USERNAME field does not contain valid data.  This field must be a string value.</invalidType>
			<invalidLength>The USERNAME field is too long.  This field must be no more than 20 bytes long.</invalidLength>
		</USERNAME>
		<EMAILADDRESS>
			<label>EMAILADDRESS</label>
			<comment/>
			<maxlength>50</maxlength>
			<notProvided>The EMAILADDRESS field is required but was not provided.</notProvided>
			<invalidType>The EMAILADDRESS field does not contain valid data.  This field must be a string value.</invalidType>
			<invalidLength>The EMAILADDRESS field is too long.  This field must be no more than 50 bytes long.</invalidLength>
		</EMAILADDRESS>
		<FIRSTNAME>
			<label>FIRSTNAME</label>
			<comment/>
			<maxlength>20</maxlength>
			<notProvided>The FIRSTNAME field is required but was not provided.</notProvided>
			<invalidType>The FIRSTNAME field does not contain valid data.  This field must be a string value.</invalidType>
			<invalidLength>The FIRSTNAME field is too long.  This field must be no more than 20 bytes long.</invalidLength>
		</FIRSTNAME>
		<userId>
			<label>userId</label>
			<comment/>
			<maxlength>22</maxlength>
			<notProvided>The userId field is required but was not provided.</notProvided>
			<invalidType>The userId field does not contain valid data.  This field must be a numeric value.</invalidType>
			<invalidLength>The userId field is too long.  This field must be no more than 22 bytes long.</invalidLength>
		</userId>
		<lastName>
			<label>lastName</label>
			<comment/>
			<maxlength>20</maxlength>
			<notProvided>The lastName field is required but was not provided.</notProvided>
			<invalidType>The lastName field does not contain valid data.  This field must be a string value.</invalidType>
			<invalidLength>The lastName field is too long.  This field must be no more than 20 bytes long.</invalidLength>
		</lastName>
		<password>
			<label>password</label>
			<comment/>
			<maxlength>20</maxlength>
			<notProvided>The password field is required but was not provided.</notProvided>
			<invalidType>The password field does not contain valid data.  This field must be a string value.</invalidType>
			<invalidLength>The password field is too long.  This field must be no more than 20 bytes long.</invalidLength>
		</password>
		<username>
			<label>username</label>
			<comment/>
			<maxlength>20</maxlength>
			<notProvided>The username field is required but was not provided.</notProvided>
			<invalidType>The username field does not contain valid data.  This field must be a string value.</invalidType>
			<invalidLength>The username field is too long.  This field must be no more than 20 bytes long.</invalidLength>
		</username>
		<emailAddress>
			<label>emailAddress</label>
			<comment/>
			<maxlength>50</maxlength>
			<notProvided>The emailAddress field is required but was not provided.</notProvided>
			<invalidType>The emailAddress field does not contain valid data.  This field must be a string value.</invalidType>
			<invalidLength>The emailAddress field is too long.  This field must be no more than 50 bytes long.</invalidLength>
		</emailAddress>
		<firstName>
			<label>firstName</label>
			<comment/>
			<maxlength>20</maxlength>
			<notProvided>The firstName field is required but was not provided.</notProvided>
			<invalidType>The firstName field does not contain valid data.  This field must be a string value.</invalidType>
			<invalidLength>The firstName field is too long.  This field must be no more than 20 bytes long.</invalidLength>
		</firstName>
	</dictionary>
